Cos Cob Power Plant Records
© 2005 University of Connecticut
- Series V: Boiler Office log sheets and repair records, 1926-1986
  - Operations Foreman's log, 1980 September 20 - 1981 February 21 (Box 13:, Folder 293)
  - Operations Foreman's log, 1984 June - 1985 March (Box 13:, Folder 294)
  - Equipment repair records, 1930s-1981 (Box 14:, Folder 295)
  - Electric meter test cards, 1950s-1960s (Box 14:, Folder 296)
  - Electric meter field test cards, 1952-1969 (Box 14:, Folder 297)
- Series VI: Power plant architectural plans (rolled plans), undated
  - Detail of steelwork for gates in intake fluke (Othertype Roll 15)
    Series 3565
    Range 1-3
  - Map of property (Othertype 16)
    3681
    17123-24854
  - Map of property (Othertype 17)
    25509-25934
  - Location of 12″ water supply from reservoir (Othertype 18)
    3682
    1-20
  - Location of 12″ water supply from reservoir (Othertype 19)
    21-32
  - Location of 12″ water supply from reservoir (Othertype 20)
    34-41
  - Addition to 11,000 volt bus & oil SW. struct. for local service feeders; Detail of drain piping at So. end of boiler room basement (Othertype 21)
    3683-84
    17002-17051
  - Addition to 11,000 volt bus & oil SW. struct. for local service feeders; Detail of drain piping at So. end of boiler room basement (Othertype 22)
    17052-17068
  - Addition to 11,000 volt bus & oil SW. struct. for local service feeders; Detail of drain piping at So. end of boiler room basement (Othertype 23)
    17073-17096
  - Addition to 11,000 volt bus & oil SW. struct. for local service feeders; Detail of drain piping at So. end of boiler room basement (Othertype 24)
    17108-17162
  - Addition to 11,000 volt bus & oil SW. struct. for local service feeders; Detail of drain piping at So. end of boiler room basement (Othertype 25)
    17168-17196
  - Addition to 11,000 volt bus & oil SW. struct. for local service feeders; Detail of drain piping at So. end of boiler room basement (Othertype 26)
    18051-19891
  - Addition to 11,000 volt bus & oil SW. struct. for local service feeders; Detail of drain piping at So. end of boiler room basement (Othertype 27)
    20001-21804
  - Addition to 11,000 volt bus & oil SW. struct. for local service feeders; Detail of drain piping at So. end of boiler room basement (Othertype 28)
    21805-24779
  - Addition to 11,000 volt bus & oil SW. struct. for local service feeders; Detail of drain piping at So. end of boiler room basement (Othertype 29)
    24853-25472
  - Addition to 11,000 volt bus & oil SW. struct. for local service feeders; Detail of drain piping at So. end of boiler room basement (Othertype 30)
    25253-25472
  - Addition to 11,000 volt bus & oil SW. struct. for local service feeders; Detail of drain piping at So. end of boiler room basement (Othertype 31)
    25612-25888
  - Addition to 11,000 volt bus & oil SW. struct. for local service feeders; Detail of drain piping at So. end of boiler room basement (Othertype 33)
    25907-29540
  - Transfer table, transformer hose (Othertype 34)
    3685
    17004-18413
  - Transfer table, transformer hose (Othertype 35)
    18556-21817
  - Transfer table, transformer hose (Othertype 36)
    24505-25998
  - Conduits & cables-Switchboard room (Othertype 37)
    3687
    1973-14—1973-20
  - Steel framing plans (Othertype 38)
    3688
    17016B-17021B
  - Steel framing plans (Othertype 39)
    17022A-17030A
  - Steel framing plans (Othertype 40)
    17030B-17060
  - Steel framing plans (Othertype 41)
    17067-17094
  - Steel framing plans (Othertype 42)
    17099-17112
  - Steel framing plans (Othertype 43)
    17113-17152
  - Steel framing plans (Othertype 44)
    17158-17192
  - Steel framing plans (Othertype 45)
    18055-18980
  - Steel framing plans (Othertype 46)
    24506x3-24511
  - Steel framing plans (Othertype 47)
    24511-24516
  - Steel framing plans (Othertype 48)
    24517Ax2-24521-B
  - Steel framing plans (Othertype 49)
    24523-24528
  - Steel framing plans (Othertype 50)
    24529-24891
  - Steel framing plans (Othertype 51)
    25481-25552
  - Steel framing plans (Othertype 52)
    25588-25871
  - Steel framing plans (Othertype 53)
    25872-25954
  - Traveling crane (Othertype 54)
    4141
    1 sheet
  - Inclined coal conveyor (Othertype 55)
    4244
    Misc.
  - Pump house (Othertype 56)
    4355
    1-8
  - Plan of roof & details (Othertype 57)
    4750
    27C—2-114
  - Plan of roof & details (Othertype 58)
    27C115-27C126
  - Plan of roof & details (Othertype 59)
    25D1—25D16
  - Plan of roof & details (Othertype 60)
    25D108-25D118
  - Plan of roof & details (Othertype 61)
    25D119-25D129
  - Plan of roof & details (Othertype 62)
    25D130-25D139
  - Plan of roof & details (Othertype 63)
    27D3-27D102
  - Plan of roof & details (Othertype 64)
    27D103-27D125
  - Plan of roof & details (Othertype 65)
    25D141—25D151, 205
  - Plan of roof & details (Othertype 66)
    25X36—25X56
  - Plan of roof & details (Othertype 67)
    25X60—25X75
  - Mianus River plant (Othertype 68)
    5604
    6124—6132
  - Mianus River plant (Othertype 69)
    6133-6172
  - Mianus River plant (Othertype 70)
    6212—6345
  - Toilet & locker room facility (Othertype 71)
    5615
    1-7
  - Profiles for water pipe lines (Othertype 72)
    6257
    4 Sheets
  - Restorage facilities (Othertype 73)
    9822
    1-5
  - Proposed bulkhead (Othertype 74)
    13921
    Stacks in East Boiler Room.
  - Prop. repairs to intake flume (Othertype 75)
    14403
  - Proposed Dam at Post Rd. Dam at Post Road (Othertype 76)
    14599, 14765
    3 Sheets
  - Mianus River dam - General site plan (Othertype 77)
    14723
    1-2
  - Mianus River dam - Foundations and trenches (Othertype 78)
    14763
    1-9
  - Sluice Gates, spillway, foundations (Othertype 79)
    14764
  - Concrete tests at Mianus River dam (Othertype 80)
    14768
    1-3 sheets
  - Water supply - Mianus dam progress chart (Othertype 81)
    14769
    2 sheets
  - Water supply - Mianus River map (Othertype 82)
    17998
    1-10
  - Floor plan of switchboard room (Othertype 83)
    18240
    1-21
  - Floor plan of switchboard room (Othertype 84)
    532-E-1—532-S1
  - Floor plan of switchboard room (Othertype 85)
    550E-2, One Line diagram of Bus Changes
    550E-3, 22KV Main Wiring Diagram
    550E-4, 11KV Main Wiring Diagram
    550E-6, Operating Wiring Diagram
    550X-7, Study of 440V Equipment
    550E-9, Wiring Diagram, Auxiliary Power – Turbine Room
    550E-9, Wiring Diagram, Auxiliary Power – Boiler Room
    550E-10, Wiring Diagram, Signal Equipment, Turbine Room
  - Floor plan of switchboard room (Othertype 86)
    550E-21, 60~ Signal Board, Wiring Diagram – Rear View
    550E-30, Control Conduits for Switch House
    550E-31 and 32, 11 KV Conduit Runs
    550E-33, Control Conduits for 11KV Buses
    550E-34, Conduits Under Switchboard Room
    550E-35, Doors for 11KV Reactor Compartments on 2nd Gallery
    550E-36, 440 Volt Switchgear Control Conduits
    550E-37, 440 Volt Power Conduits at Switchgear
    550E-38, 440 Volt Feeder Conduit Layout
    550E-39, Details of Wood Blocks
  - Floor plan of switchboard room (Othertype 87)
    550-E-40/41, Plan view of Control Room
    550-E-42, Plan view of East Boiler Room
    550-E-43, Panel dimensions
    550-E-44, Elevation view of Field Circuit-breakers
    550-E-45, Plan view of 440 Volt Switchgear
    550-E-46, Emergency Signal Circuit-breakers
    550-E-47, Elevation view of local Service Transformers
    550-E-48, Termination of Generator leads
    550-E-49, Panel details
  - Floor plan of switchboard room (Othertype 88)
    550-E-50, WD, Recording meters panel
    550-E-51, Section and Elecvation views of Bus connections to cables and switches
    550-E-52, Bus connections to Generator Circuit-breakers
    550-E-53, Plan view of Back Bus
    550-E-54, Section view through Back Bus
    550-E-55, Star Bus Reactor connections
    550-E-56, Section view through Front and Back Bus sections
    550-E-57, Plan view of Back Bus
    550-E-58, 22KV Out-Door switches
    550-E-59, Connection of cables from Track-circuits at Switch house
  - Floor plan of switchboard room (Othertype 89)
    550-E-60, 22 KV Bus assembly
    550-E-61, Plan view of 22KV Buses
    550-E-62, Elecvation view of cable-connections between Traction-Power transformers and Dis-Connect switches
    550-E-63, Section view across Switch house looking North
    550-E-64, Elevation view of Bus connections to 22KV Circuit-breakers
    550-E-65, Plan and elevation view of Traction-Power transformers
    550-E-66, Elevation view of Dis-Connect switches for 22KV Circuit-breakers
    550-E-67, Plan view of Switch house
    550-E-68/69, Pull-Box for cables from Generator No. 3
    550-E-70, Plan view of Switch house
  - Floor plan of switchboard room (Othertype 90)
    550-E-71/72/73, 22KV Bus supports
    550-E-74, Transite barriers
    550-E-75, Circuit-breaker supports
    550-E-77, WD, D.C. power
    550-E-78, WD, Synchronization
    550-E-79, WD, Exciter Switchboard
  - Floor plan of switchboard room (Othertype 91)
    550-E-80, Plan and elevation views of West Farms Tie-Circuits in Switch house
    550-E-81, 22KV Outdoor switches
    550-E-82, Panel details
    550-E-83, Plan view of Power house and Switch house South of Turbine Hall
    550-E-84, WD, 11KV Bus differential protective relay scheme
    550-E-85, Plan view of Power house and Switch house South of Turbine Hall
    550-E-86, 22KV Outdoor switches
    550-E-87, Plan view of Front and Back BU sections and Local service transformers
    550-E-88, Plan view of Switch house
    550-E-89, Plan view of 440 Volt Switchgear
  - Floor plan of switchboard room (Othertype 92)
    550-E-90, Plan view of compartments where generator leads terminated on current transformers
    550-E-91, Plan view of Power house and Switch house South of Turbine Hall
    550-E-92, Plan view of transformers
    550-E-93, Control room details
    550-E-94, Plan view of Control room
    550-E-95, 60 cycle motor generator set
    550-E-96, 22KV outdoor switches
    550-E-98, Plan view of Back Bus
    550-E-99, Motor generator set
    550-E-100, WD, Recording meters panel
    550-E-101, WD, 1-Line D.C. power
    550-E-102, Elevation view of Generator No. 3 pull box over Bus structure
  - Floor plan of switchboard room (Othertype 93)
    611 S8-2—634 S2
  - Boiler instal. - main & aux steam piping (Othertype 94)
    18241
    456-S-1D5-456-S-10-D4
  - Boiler instal. - main & aux steam piping, 1942 (Othertype 95)
    456-S11-D3, Basement Flood – Boiler room, Walls and Floor to be Removed
    456-S12-D5, Plan of Boiler Platform, Gratings
    456-S13-D3, Foundation Plan and Details for Stack Precipitator and Substation
    456-S14-D3, Substation and Walkways
    456-S15-D4, Structural Steel Details, Operating Floor and Coal Larry Level
    456-S16-D4, Structural Steel Details, Operating Floor
    456-S17-D3, Structural Steel Details, Operating Floor
    456-S18-D2, Structural Steel Details, Stairs
    456-S19-D2, Structural Steel Details, East Wall
    456-S20-D1, Structural Steel Details, East Wall
  - Boiler instal. - main & aux steam piping (Othertype 96)
    456-21D4-456-32D1
  - Boiler instal. - main & aux steam piping (Othertype 97)
    456-E-1,D3—456-E90-2
  - Boiler instal. - main & aux steam piping (Othertype 98)
    456-M-1C—456-M-10E
  - Boiler instal. - main & aux steam piping (Othertype 99)
    456-X-19—456B-54C
  - Emergency Connection with G.W.Co (Othertype 100)
    14747
  - Embankment Protection
    47019
  - Contour map of Mianus
    14399
  - River Valley
    17352X53-60
  - Water supply: valve chamber
    5398
  - Det. vicinity of power house
  - Proposed Bypass
    14401
    17352
  - Survey at coal handling crane (Othertype 101)
    14410
  - Intake Flume
    14169
  - Additional water supply
    14395
    13787X2.
  - Fly-ash bank (Othertype 102)
    46930
  - Instal. of overflow pipe & fly-ash storage tank
    46957
  - Cos Cob Power Plant
    13851
    2991
  - 5700 gal. oil tank spill cont. berm
    46993
  - Cross sections at prop. struct. locations
    46745
  - Prop. pipeline from Mianus River (Othertype 103)
    14398
  - 16″ pipeline inlet crossing - Mianus River dam
    5399
  - Cos Cob wat. supply - Mianus
    14741
  - River Dam 10″ drain - E. of Bridge - Boston Post Rd. Additional water supply piping
    14400
  - River Dam 10″ drain - E. of Bridge - Boston Post Rd. Additional water supply piping
    14396
  - Prop. pipeline from Mianus River
  - Pipeline blow off - Mianus River dam
    5401-1-2